

SOFTWARE ENGINEER/FULLSTACK.NET DEVELOPER

DAYÁN RUIZ

PROFILE

Software Enginner/Full Stack .NET Developer with more than five years of experience in web development. Passion for learning, coding, improve my skills and grow professionally.

Looking for new challenges and extremely motivated for being Head of Software Engineering.

CONTACT

Montevideo, Uruguay

dayanrr91@gmail.com

+598 93668048

in /dayan-ruiz-riera

SKILLS

C#: Advanced

ASP.NET MVC: Advanced

ASP.NET Web Api: Advanced

SQL: Upper-Intermediate

AngularJS: Advanced

ReactJS: Intermediate

Javascript: Advanced

WORK EXPERIENCE

FullStack .NET Developer

MIDDLESOFT | OCT 2019 - PRESENT

- Web development using C#, ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET CORE, JQuery, SQL Server, HTML and CSS.
- Collaborate with web developer teams in architecture, backend and frontend tasks.
- Direct communication with clients, including demo and deploys.

FullStack .NET Developer

ONETREE | MAR 2017 - OCT 2019

- Web development using C#, ASP.NET MVC, AngularJS, SQL Server, HTML and CSS.
- Collaborate with web developer teams in architecture, backend and frontend tasks.
- Direct communication with clients, always in english.

FRONTEND Developer - Part-time

FREELANCER | APR 2019 - OCT 2019

- Frontend development using HTML, CSS, ReactJS and Redux.
- Collaborate with web developer teams in frontend tasks.
- Direct communication with clients.

JQuery: Intermediate

Angular 2+: Intermediate

HTML: Advanced

CSS: Upper-Intermediate

SCRUM: Advanced

Git: Advanced

Entity Framework: Intermediate

Dapper: Advanced

SQL-Server: Upper-Intermediate

EDUCATION

University of Informatics Sciences Software Engineer, 2019-2014

LANGUAGE

English: Advanced

Spanish: Native

FRONTEND Developer - Part-time

SOYUZLABS | JUN 2018 - DEC 2018

- Frontend development using HTML, CSS and Angular 6.
- Collaborate with web developer teams in architecture, and frontend tasks.

FullStack .NET Developer

SOPHILABS | MAY 2016 - MAR 2017

- Web development using C#, ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET WebApi and SQL Server, HTML and CSS.
- Collaborate with web developer teams in backend and frontend tasks.

Web Developer - Part-time

UNIVERSIDAD DE LAS CIENCIAS INFORMÁTICAS | SEP 2014 - MAR 2016

- Using technologies like Java, Spring, HTML and CSS.
- Construction and maintainance of a monitoring module for an open source tool.
- Collaborate with web developer teams in backend and frontend tasks.